// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The appearance of Date and Time depends upon the ____________ applied to the cell?",
    answer: "Format",
    options: [
      "Design",
      "Format",
      "Layout",
      "Setup"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: " To turn on Overtype mode _________ key is to be pressed from keyboard?",
    answer: "Insert",
    options: [
      "Delete",
      "Insert",
      "Shift",
      "Enter"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following languages are machine dependent?",
    answer: "Machine and Assembly Language",
    options: [
      "Machine and Assembly Language",
      "Machine and Fourth Generation Language",
      "Fourth Generation and High Level Language",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "A program written in Assembly Language is called as __________?",
    answer: "Source Program",
    options: [
      "Object Program",
      "Object Code",
      "Source Program",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " ___________ is the shortcut key to undo the last action?",
    answer: "Ctrl + Z",
    options: [
      "Ctrl + X",
      "Ctrl + Z",
      "Ctrl + A",
      "Ctrl + C"
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Which function key is used to modify the contents within a cell?",
      answer: "F2",
      options: [
        "F2",
        "F1",
        "F9",
        "F4"
      ]
  },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "Which of the following is not a feature of Fourth Generation Language?",
      answer: "Machine dependent",
      options: [
        "Machine dependent",
        "User friendly",
        "High speed of execution",
        "Application development tools"
      ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "We can select adjacent rows/column in a worksheet by using _______key.",
    answer: "Shift",
    options: [
      "Ctrl",
      "Enter",
      "Shift",
      "Tab"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "________ key combination can be used to minimise a workbook window to an icon.",
    answer: "Ctrl + F9",
    options: [
      "Shift + F9",
      "Ctrl + F9",
      "Shift + F10",
      "Ctrl + F10"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: " C++ is an example of __________ language",
    answer: "High level",
    options: [
      "Machine",
      "High level",
      "Assembly",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "__________ release refers to a product that is still in development but released for testing purpose.",
    answer: "Beta",
    options: [
      "Alpha",
      "Beta",
      "Gamma",
      "Pie"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Which language is directly understood by computers and does not require to be translated?",
    answer: "Machine language",
    options: [
      "Assembly language",
      "Machine language",
      "High level language",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: " ___________ was the first interactive computer game.",
    answer: "Spacewar",
    options: [
      "Minecraft",
      "PubG",
      "Firewatch",
      "Spacewar"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "A programmer is using 0's and 1's to write the program. Which generation of computer languages is he/ she using ?",
    answer: "First",
    options: [
      "First",
      "Third",
      "Fourth",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: " The _________ and ___________ buttons are present on the Formula bar.",
    answer: "Cancel , Enter",
    options: [
      "Cancel , Enter",
      "Enter , Insert",
      "Insert , Enter",
      "Cancel , Insert"
    ]
  },
  
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 16,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];